Guide to the Stanford University, School of Humanities and Sciences, Innovative Academic Courses, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records, Accession ARCH-1992-086
  - SWOP 161 Bomb, Star Wars, Tech. Fix., Fall 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - SWOP 163 Animal Rights and Research Fall 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - SWOP 164 Democracy Beyond Ballot Box, Fall 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - SWOP 165 Developing Constructive Alternatives to the Military Economy, Fall 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - SWOP 168 Politics of Gender and Sexuality, Fall 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - SWOP 174A Issues in Self Defense for Women, Fall 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - SWOP 175 Women's Movement Today (1 unit) Fall 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - SWOP 185 Sactuary Movement, Fall 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - SWOP 187 Perpsectives on Election Issues, Fall 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - SWOP 191 Education: A Tool for Social and Community Development, Fall 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Street Theater and Performance Art Workshop, Catanzarite 1/31/87 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - SWOP 134 Eyes on the Prize, Winter 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - SWOP 136 Images of American Indians Winter 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - SWOP 162 Culture and Politics in the Nuclear Age, Winter, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - SWOP 166, Politics of Social Movements, Winter 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - SWOP 174 Issues in Self Defense for Women, Winter 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - SWOP 176 Men, Women, and Feminism, Winter 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - SWOP 190 Issues Surrounding Homeless Youth, Winter1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - SWOP 191 Education A Tool for Social and Community Development, Winter 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - SWOP 192 Working Effectively with Disturbed Children, Winter 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - SWOP 130 Minorities in Higher Education, Spring 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - SWOP 183: Taking apart the War Machine, Winter 1976 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - SWOP 132: Asian American Women... Spring 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - SWOP 133 Criminal Procedure and the Special Problem of Race, Spring 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - SWOP 140 El Salvador Project, Spring 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - SWOP 142 Hunger in The Land of Plenty, Spring 1987 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - SWOP 143 The International Protection of Human Rights, Spring 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - SWOP 167 Workers Cooperatives and Workplace Democracy, Spring 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - SWOP 170 Balancing Work and Family Life, Spring 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - SWOP 171 On Women, Contemporary Issues and Choices, Spring 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - SWOP 174A Issues in Self-Defense for Women, Spring 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - SWOP 192A Working Effectively with Disturbed Children, Spring 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - SWOP 193 Deaf Studies, Spring 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Asian American Women, Spring 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - SWOP 169 Our Jobs, Our Community: Stoping Plant Closures, Spring 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - SWOP 143 The International Protection of Human Rights Fall 1986-1987 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - SWOP 150 Preventing War: Discussing Arms Controls Issues Fall 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - SWOP 151 American Indians in Higher Education, Fall 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - SWOP 152 Sustainable Agriculture, Fall 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - SWOP 153 Race, Racism, and American Society, Fall 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - SWOP 154 The Politics of AIDS: Fear and Loathing in the US, Fall 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - SWOP 155 Toxic Wastes and the Law: Society's Problem... Fall 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - SWOP 169 Our Jobs, Our Community: Plant Closures, Fall 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - SWOP 174A Issues in Self-Defense for Women, Fall 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - SWOP 191 Education: Tool for Social Change and Development, Fall 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - SWOP 110 The History of East Palo Alto, Winter 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - SWOP 111 The Living Environment: Ethical Perspectives, Winter 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - SWOP 112 Asian American Literature, Winter 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - SWOP 113 The US and South Africa: Race, Racism and Apartheid, Winter 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - SWOP 114 Chicano Poetics, Winter 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - SWOP 115 Gay Male Literature, Winter 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - SWOP 116 Native American Religion/ Philosophy/ Spirituality, Winter 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - SWOP 117 Medicine and Law: Boundary Issues: Winter 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - SWOP 166 The 1960's and its Legacy, Winter 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - SWOP 174A Issues in Self-Defense for Women Winter Quarter 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Spring General Info. 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Spring 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - SWOP 131 The Urban Polics: Poltical Justice in... Spring 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - SWOP 135 Murals as a Socio-Political Statement, Sping 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - SWOP 141 Central American Education Project, Spring 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - SWOP 166 The 60's: A decade of Activism, Sping 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - SWOP 174A Issues in Self Defense for Women, Sping 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - SWOP 177 California Tomorrow: Our Changing State, Sping 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - SWOP 180 The United States-Mexico Border Sping 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - SWOP 188 Presidential Campaigning Sping 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - SWOP 189 Current Ethical And Social Issues in Employment Spring 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - SWOP 192 Working Effectivly with Disturbed Children, Sping 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - SWOP 193 Literacy and Liberation, Sping 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Fall Quarter, General Information, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - SWOP 101: The Politics of Health Care in the Developing World, Fall 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - SWOP 102: African American Liberation Music, Fall 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - SWOP 103: THe Disability Rights Movement, Fall 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - SWOP 104: Society Behind Bars, Fall 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - SWOP 105: Native American Activism, Fall 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - SWOP 106: US Media and World Politics, Fall 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - SWOP 107: Rape Education Seminar (MC) Fall 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - SWOP 154: The Politics of AIDS, Fall 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - SWOP 163: The Case for Animal Rights, Fall 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - 174A Issues in Self Defense for Women, Fall 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Winter Quarter Information, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - SWOP 121: Asian American Experience, Winter 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - SWOP 122 Homelessness in America Winter 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - SWOP 123: International Refuge Crisis, Winter 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - SWOP 124: Medicine and Law, Winter 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - SWO P125: The Affects of War: Refugees in Indochina, Winter 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - SWOP 126: Vietnam Vets and Vietnamese Winter 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - SWOP 174: Self Defense Winter 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Spring Quarter General Information, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - SWOP 130: Current Issues in Gender and Sexuality, Spring1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - SWOP 133: Cirriculum and Instruction for the Immagrant: Spring 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - SWOP 135: Gay Male Literature, Spring 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - SWOP 138 Multicultural Education, Spring 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - SWOP 141: Palestinians: Lives in Art Spring 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - SWOP 144 Racism on College Campuses: Spring 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 68)
  - SWOP 147: The Unseen America Spring 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 69)
  - SWOP 149 Anarchist Theory and Practice: Spring 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 70)
  - SWOP 174A Self Defense Spring 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 71)
  - Proposal for Ford Foundation Support of Stanford Workshops on Political and Socal Issues (SWOPSI) (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - The Politics of Technology (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - The Pescardero Dam and San Mateo County Coastside Development, January 1970 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Air Pollution in the San Fransisco Bay Area (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Air Pollution in the San Fransisco Bay Area, Condensed Report, Summer, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Privacy and Student Records at Stanford University, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Logging in Urban Counties, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Pesticide Exposure and Protection of California Farm Workers, November 1970 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - The Politics of Technology, A Report by SWOPSI (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - A Summary of The Gates Commision Report (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - D.O.D. Sponsored Research At Stanford, Volume I, A Report By SWOPSI [typescript version] (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Master Photocopy of D.O.D. Sponsered Research At Stanford, Volume I, A Report By SWOPSI (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - D.O.D. Sponsored Research At Stanford, Volume II, A Report By SWOPSI [smaller publ. version] (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Balanced Transportation Planning for Suburban and Academis Communities, SWOPSI (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - The Politics of Pollution Control in Monteray Bay (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Congress and Technology (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Ride On (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Ride On (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - The Independence of "The Stanford Daily", A SWOPSI Report, December 1971 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Balanced Transportation Planning for Stanford University, SWOPSI, December 1971 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - A Report of the Special Joint Agencies of the Academic Senate, November 1972 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Bay Area Housing, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Making Daycare More than Baysitting, SWOP 142, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - The Other Stanford, SWOPSI (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Balanced Transportation Planning for Suburban and Academic Communities (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Public Transportation of the San Fransisco Penninsula: Should BART be Expanded? (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Varsity Atheletics, The Black Community and Stanford University, April 1974 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Rapid Transit and the Public Interest (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Designs for Alternative Life Styles, Better Homes and Garbage, SWOPSI 185, June 1974 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - A Guide To Off Campus Living (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Progressive Instructors (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - A Report to The National Institute of Social Sciences, 1975-1976 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - The California Nucelar Initiative Debate (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Working Against Rape (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Off-Campus Tenants: Landlords to Watch Out For (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - EVERYTHING California Tenants Need to Know about Getting Back their SECURITY DEPOSITS (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Instructor's Handbooks, 1979, 1984, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Preserving and Revilalizing Historical Area, SWOP 190, Winter 1976-1977, "but that was such a nice old house." (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Approaching Wilderness, a conservation handbook (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Women and Science, A bibliographical Resource (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Working Against Rape (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Working Against Rape, Supplementary Information (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - UGS Instructor's Handbook (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - SWOPSI Instructor's Handbook (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Curriculum and Instruction for the Immigrant Student, SWOP 133: Urgent Care for ESL/Civics Teachers (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - A Profile of Residents Living in The Single Room Occupancy Hotels of Palo Alto (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - The Homelessness of America, SWOPSI 122: Hansen Act Report (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Hardvard-Radcliffe East Wind, Spring 1989 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Razing Cane, Spring 1989 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Voices, Asian American Women's Journal, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - SWOPSI Archives: Co-Operative Living at Stanford (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - SWOPSI Publications list, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - The Other Isreal, July 1983 - September 1988 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - UGS 1, Winter Quarter 1989 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Politics of Health Care, SWOP 101, Fall 1988 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Introduction to Curriculum: Policy Focus, SWOPSI 216, Education 208X, Summer 1988 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - A Decade of Activism, The 1960's in America, SWOP 166, Spring 1988 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Campus Environmental Audit (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Edwards/Dugarm, UGS 11, Winter 1988 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - The Asian American Experience: a psychological perspective, SWOP 121, Winter 1989 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Homelessness of America, SWOP 122, Winter 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Medicine and Law, Winter Quarter 1988-1989, Volume I (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Medicine and Law, Winter Quarter 1988-1989, Volume II (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Issues in Self-Defense for Women, SWOP 174A, Winer 1988-1989, Volume I (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Issues in Self-Defense for Women, SWOP 174A, Winer 1988-1989, Volume II (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Hindu Mythology, Spring 1989 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Medical Models, Spring 1989 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Non-Violence and Social Change, SWOP 173, Fall 1989-1990 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Self-Defense- SWOP 174-A, Fall 1989-1990 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Body Image and Eating Issues, SWOP 178, Autumn, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Body Image and Eating Issues, SWOP 178, Autumn, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - SWOP 178, Papers, Autumn, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Environmental Degradation and Social Change, SWOP 179, Fall 1989-1990 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Class Ethnicity and Sexuality, SWOP 183, Fall 1989-1990 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Papers and Reports (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Papers for Artificial People, FSS 008, Winter Quarter 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Racism on College Campuses, SWOP 144, Winter 1990 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Alvarez/ Lee SWOP 144, Winter 1990 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - The Earthquake of October 17, 1979, SWOP Winter Quarter 1990 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Wang, SWOP 158, Winter 1990 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Tom Henning, Spring 1990 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Lise Grande, Spring 1990 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Suha Jhaveri, Spring 1990 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Unvollendete Geschichte translated into English, UGS 054: Spring Quarter 1990 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Perspectives on East Palo Alto and the Problems of Poor Minority Communities, UGS 57, Spring 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - The Social Impact of Miltarism, SWOP 012, Winter 1991 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Contemporary Issues in the Asian American Community: Challenging the Model Minority Myth, SWOP 156, Winter 1991 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - UGS 101, Winter 1991 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Feminist Epistemology, Final Papers, UGS 104, Winter 1991 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Introduction to Multicultural Literature and Writing, SWOP 104, Winter 1991 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Multicultural Training Program, SWOP 104, Winter 1991 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Stanford University Response to DCAA Adit Report Number 731-90U43510004 (0353), Volume I, Stanford Response,Winter 1991 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Stanford University Response to DCAA Adit Report Number 731-90U43510004 (0353), Volume II, Additonal Supporting Documents, Winter 1991 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Introduction to Creative Writing, SWOP 104, Winter 1991 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Introduction to Creative Writing, SWOP 104, Winter 1991 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Issues in Self-Defense For Women, SWOP 174A, Spring 1991 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - PC: 306, SWOP 216, Spring 1991 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - PC: 311, SWOP 216, Spring 1991 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - PC: 313, SWOP 216, Spring 1991 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - PC: 316, SWOP 216, Spring 1991 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Feminist Approaches to Contemporary Masculinity, Feminist Studies, 172, Spring Quarter 1990-1991 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - American Voices, UGS 212, Spring 1991 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Masculinity and War, SWOP 210, Spring 1991 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Spatial Systems and Social Processes, SOC 267, Spring 1991 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - PC: 570, SWOP 216, Spring 1991 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - PC: 571, SWOP 216, Spring 1991 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - PC: 572, SWOP 216, Spring 1991 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - PC: 573, SWOP 216, Spring 1991 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - PC: 574, SWOP 216, Spring 1991 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - PC: 575, SWOP 216, Spring 1991 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - PC: 576, SWOP 216, Spring 1991 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - PC: 598, SWOP 216, Spring 1991 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - PC: 602, SWOP 216, Spring 1991 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - PC: 603, SWOP 216, Spring 1991 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - PC: 605, SWOP 216, Spring 1991 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - PC: 606, SWOP 216, Spring 1991 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - PC: 607, SWOP 216, Spring 1991 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - PC: 608, SWOP 216, Spring 1991 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - PC: 609, SWOP 216, Spring 1991 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - PC: 610, SWOP 216, Spring 1991 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - SWOP 031, Fall 1991 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Writers from the Other Europe, Post-War Eastern European Writers in Perspective, UGS 102, Fall Quarter, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - PC: 247, Fall 1991 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - PC: 248, Fall 1991 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - PC: 249, Fall 1991 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - PC: 250, Fall 1991 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - PC: 251, Fall 1991 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - PC: 252, Fall 1991 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - PC: 253, Fall 1991 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - PC: 254, Fall 1991 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - PC: 255, Fall 1991 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - PC: 256, Fall 1991 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - PC: 257, Fall 1991 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - SWOP 22, Fall 1991 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - UGS 112, Winter 1991 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - US Policy Response to Latin American Immigration, SWOP 75, Spring 1992 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Gender, Communication and Sexual Violence, SWOP 93, Spring 1992 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - History of the African American Family Since 1965, UGS 75, Spring 1992 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Lesbian Feminist Poetry, UGS 82, Spring 1992 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Death Penalty, Student Notebooks (6 total) (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Death Penalty, Student Notebooks (7 total) (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - SWOPSI Student Reports and Papers, 1990-1992 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Violence in the Family, SWOP 13 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - A Special Relationship: US Involvement in the Philippines, SWOP 18 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Waite and Gershman, SWOP 18 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Dorf and Sassaman, SWOP 033 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Environmental Degradation and Social Change, SWOP 179 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - American Violence: The Gun Connection, UGS 011 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Cross Cultural Representation in Postcolonial Period, UGS 16 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Palestinians and their Society, 1998-1946, A Photographic Essay (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - PC: 499, UGS 5, Ramanelli (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - PC: 500, UGS 5, Ramanelli (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - PC: 501, UGS 5, Ramanelli (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - The Stanford Environmental Audit, A Centennial Project, A Mid Year Report, February 4, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - SWOPSI Handbook on Instructor Workshops (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Stanford University Student Organization Sourcebook, 1989-1990 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Resources for Activities (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - University Committee on Minority Issues (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Stanford, 100 Years (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Building a Multiracial, Multicultural University Community (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - A Woman's Guide to Stanford (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Research for Action, A Guidebook to Public Records Investigation for Community Activists (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Resources for Change: A Guide to Projects 1978-1979 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Teaching At Stanford, An Introductory Handbook (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Reading Lists in Radical Social Science (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - People Power: What Communities are Doing to Counter Inflation (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Directory of Socially Responsible Investments (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Handbook for Teaching Assistants at Stanford (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Language, Gender and Professional Writing (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - No More Public School (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - The Craft of Teaching (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Taking Sides, Clashing Views on Controversial Educational Issues (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Teaching Tips (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Preparing Instructional Objectives (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Booker T. Washintgon and His Crisis (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Five Acres and Independence (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - The Black Seventies (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - The Mis-Education of the Negro (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Revolution in Central America (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Wheeling Your Way Through San Jose and Other Cities in Santa Clara County (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - An Irreverent, Illustrated View of Nuclear Power (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Sexual Assult on Campus: What Colleges Can Do (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Taking Action: What to do if you are Raped (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Being Safe: Protecting Yourself, You Family and Your Home (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Lesbian Studies (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Nuclear California (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - The Silent Bomb (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Nutrition Intervention in Developing Countires (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Quality-Protein Maize (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Vegetable Research and Development in SADCC Countries (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - New Burlington, The Life and Death of an American Village (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Natural Family Planning (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - UGS 107, Fall 1991 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Vote Yes on 128- Big Green (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - SWOPSI 20 Year Reunion, 1st Director: Nicholas Corff (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Beyond the Walls, Defining Moments, Arab: 3, Perspectives, Betsy Thompson (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Apple Computer Disks (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Latin Films Forum, February 29, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Multi-Cultural Education Side 1 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Multi-Cultural Education, Side 3 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - SWOPSI Evaluations 1972 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - SWOPSI Evaluations 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - SWOPSI Evaluations 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - SWOPSI Course Evaluations and Course Information, Spring 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Final Evaluations Fall 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Final Evaluations Winter 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Annual Report 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Final Evaluations Spring 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Final Evaluations Fall 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Final Evaluations Winter 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Final Evaluations Spring 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - End of Quarter Evaluation Forms: Instructors (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Student Mid- Quarter Evaluation Forms (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Evaluations (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Evaluations 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Final Evaluations Fall 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Final evaluations Winter 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Final Evaluations Spring 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Evaluation Forms Random Sample n=35 1975-1977 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Mid-Quarter Evaluations Fall 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Final Evaluations Fall 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Mid-Quarter Evaluations Winter 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Final Evaluations Winter 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Summary of Instructor Mid-Quarter Evaluations 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Mid-Quarter Evaluation Spring 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Final Evaluations Spring 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Mid-Quarter Evaluations Fall 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - End Quarter Evaluations Fall 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Index of End-Quarter Evaluations Fall 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Mid-Quarter Evaluations Winter 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Index of Mid-Quarter Evaluations Winter 1978-1979 (Box 31, Folder 9)